I thought it was good.
I'm not saying that the movie wasn't
good, it was, I enjoyed it, just...
heist movies aren't really
my thing.
I know, I know. I forgot,
you're more of a... you're more
of a romcom girl.
I am not.
Grace, I've known you since
you were 14,
you love romcoms more
than anyone I know.
I don’t know if it’s that.
I think it's just...
I like the idea of two people deciding
that they're better off together
than they are apart...
and a happy ending
Ergo, you love romcoms.
Okay, fine.
I got to get back to the office
to do some work,
but I had such a great time.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
I guess until the next time one
of us needs a plus one.
Mm, sure.
You're a good friend, Quinn.
- Have a good night, Grace.
- You too.
Yes, we're doing the eggshells shiplap
on the far wall to match the Carrera
marble in the kitchen.
Mm, I'll pick up the backsplash
samples later today.
That is not our job. Sorry.
Uh-huh, I look forward to
the design coming together too.
Chat soon.
Hey, did you finish the mood
boards for Hannah’s tree?
Yeah, I sure did, I have them
back at the office.
Oh, amazing. Listen, I am swamped today,
would you mind running them over to her?
- Yeah, you got it.
- Thank you.
Can we get three hot chocolates, please?
Great. Yes.
What's that?
Ooh. Operation “Complete Jack’s Baseball
Card Collection” is now... well, complete.
Complete as in?
Complete as in, on Christmas morning,
he's going to wake up to every rookie card
from the year he was born.
You’re too good to him.
- You know I love a mission.
I know you do.
Oh, did you see the email?
I did, yeah, the one about us decorating
the Town Square Christmas tree
in less than three days?
Hey, come on, we can do it.
We've done bigger jobs than that,
and that was less notice,
less time.
Yeah. I mean, I guess since
we didn't get the full decorating
contract from Sami...
She wants us to call her Mayor
Hoffman now.
Oh, yeah, of course. It's so weird that
she's our mayor.
I mean, we're the same age,
that just makes me feel old.
I know, but hey, she threw us a bone by
getting us that contract on the tree,
so we should at least try
to call her by her official title.
Yeah, and in the email that I saw,
she's gonna provide all these city
employees to help us out.
We don't need that.
I think we need all the hands
we can get.
Yeah, maybe you're right, but you know
what?
If we pull this off, next year,
the entire town Ivy Glen
could be designed and decorated
by Keen and Rankin.
That would be...
Everything we dreamed of when
we started our business!
- Yes! It is, yes.
- I know!
Holy cricket!
Oh, stop that! Just leave it!
Ryan St. Nicholas.
You sound so official.
So do you, Madame Mayor.
How goes your reign in our quaint
hometown?
It's been better. I'm actually calling
to ask you a favour... from an old friend.
What's up?
The St. Nicholas House.
My grandmother's house?
You still own it, right?
For now, yes. Why?
Um... I have a bit of
a situation.
So, Ivy Glen's charities are
in a bit of a pinch.
Normally, Christmas time
is our busiest time,
but now, donating is down
over 50 percent.
Inflation, recession,
everyone's feeling the pinch.
Which doesn't look good for
a young first-term mayor.
Or someone who cares about
their hometown.
Look, it's affecting so many
organizations, especially the food bank.
I wouldn't ask if it wasn't an
emergency, but...
have you considered reviving your
grandmother's Ribbons and Bows Fundraiser?
- Uh...
I don't know, not really
in my wheelhouse.
Even if it would so much good
for the town and honour your family's
tradition?
Okay, okay.
I'll... I'll consider it. I...
was thinking about coming back home
for the holidays
anyway to tie up a few things.
Well, let me know as soon as you can,
please, I'm on a bit of a timeline.
Oh, will do, Sami.
I believe that's Mayor
Hoffman to you.
Oh, sorry, Madame Mayor.
Kayla?
- Yes?
Will you book me that flight
back to Ivy Glen?
Of course.
I think I’m going to head home
for Christmas after all.
Right away.
That was a long cocoa run.
Well, I had to complete operation "Make
Christmas magical for my husband."
- So, you found my race car?
- Yeah, and the track to go with it.
Hi.
Mom called, said she and dad arrived in
Italy and are having a great time.
Told me to tell you she got the fabric
samples from...
- Giuseppe?
- Giuseppe, yeah. Who's Giuseppe?
That's amazing. He is a draper in
Tuscany
and he hand-weaves all these
intricate patterns.
I wanted to use the samples for the mood
boards on the Balzerini’s living room
so that I can tie in their heritage
to the new space.
- Great.
- Yes! I love that.
All right here.
Ooh, but we should probably focus on
the Christmas tree design.
Okay. I was thinking lots of lights.
Lights, okay.
Love it. What else?
That's as far as I got.
Okay.
Ahh...
Hm...
Well, let me give it some thought.
Where are you going?
We just got here.
Yes, well, I need inspiration.
So, I'll see you both later.
- Bye, sis.
- Good luck. I'll see you soon.
So, about that race car...
Okay, no peeking.
No before Christmas.
Hey, Maggie.
Yes, I saw your email.
Yeah. No, I... I'm in Ivy Glen
as we speak.
I will get the house all set up and
we should be ready to list in a few days.
Uh... I gotta go.
No way.
- I'm... so sorry. Um...
Ryan?
Grace.
Hi. What...
Why are you looking at me
like that?
Just... what are you doing
here?
I just came back to tie up
a few things.
Wow, must be a pretty big deal if it
brought you all the way back
from New York City to our
humble little town.
It's been... what, 15 years?
Five, actually. I came back to help move
my nan out of the St. Nicholas House
so she could live closer
to me in New York.
Right. I heard. I'm... so sorry
I couldn't be there, Ryan.
I loved your grandmother,
I was just...
I was out of state working with
a client and...
It's okay, I heard.
It is really good to see you.
Yeah, it's good to see you
too. You look...
very professional.
- And you look...
- More mature?
Exactly the same.
Oh.
Um... so, are you staying
for Christmas, or...
- I'm considering it.
- Hmm.
We should hang out
if you're free.
Yeah... no... it's actually my busy time
of the year,
so I don't know if we can
work it out, but...
Okay.
You know, my number is still the same,
though, so call me or text me.
Have your people call my people,
we can set something up.
Okay.
- Anyway, I should probably run.
I just was trying to get some
inspiration.
Olivia and I are actually in charge
of decorating the tree this year,
but we only have a few days, so...
It's going well, I see.
Stop it, I'm just getting
started.
Well, I can't wait to see what
you guys do with it.
Thanks.
So, I guess I'll see you around.
Yeah. Well, it's a small town,
so it's highly likely.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- What are you up to?
- Oh, just procrastinating instead of
designing that Christmas tree.
- Ooh, I had a really good idea.
- Uh-uh?
- Woodland creatures.
- Ooh.
Yeah, so we could have like all these
little critters running around the tree.
Wait, you don't mean live
animals, do you?
The idea sounded better in
my head.
Sami! Mayor Hoffman.
Hi.
To what do we owe the pleasure?
Oh, I'm so sorry I can't stay long,
but I have an urgent request
that I wanted to ask in person.
- What's up?
- Do you remember Ribbons and Bows
Fundraiser?
On Christmas Eve.
The one Mrs. St. Nicholas used to host
every year? Yeah, what about it?
We're reviving it.
Well, I'm trying to revive it.
Ryan isn't quite on board yet,
so I was hoping you could talk
to him.
- Uh...
- Ryan? Like...
Ryan St. Nicholas? That Ryan?
- Mm-hmm.
- I think he's in New York.
- He's actually in Ivy Glen right now.
- What?
- I was really hoping you could help me.
Maybe you could talk to him
and see if you can get him on board.
You know what? The Ribbons and Bows
Fundraiser really was his nan's thing,
so if he's not into it, then...
Oh, a lot of people in town could really
use this. It could do a lot of good.
Hmm... and you two are close.
We were close. Then, he went off
to New York
and he created this whole life
I know nothing about.
Well, he would still listen to you.
Could you just try? Please.
I wouldn't ask if it wasn't urgent.
- I don't know.
How about this? I know that this year,
the decorating contract went to Mark
and his team,
as it does every year for
as long as I can remember,
but he's retiring. It's gonna be
up for grabs next year,
so if you can help me get Ryan to host
this year's Ribbons and Bows Fundraiser,
it'll go a long way to seeing that you get
the contract from town council next year.
Okay. How about this?
You will personally guarantee...
Yes, that we will be the top candidate
next year for the contract
if we can get the house
decorated in less than a week?
Sure.
- We'll discuss it.
- We're in.
She's definitely in.
- Okay.
Okay, great. Thank you.
Oh, you two are lifesavers.
- Happy to help.
- Bye, Jack.
Bye, Mayor.
Okay. Umm... wow.
Hmm, looks like you have to get
to St. Nicholas House.
Yeah, looks like I do, uh? I guess I'll
give you guys an update when I get back.
Ryan.
Stop it, Jack!
Huh.
I know that look.
- I have an idea.
- Oh, no.
Not, "Oh, no." Oh, yes!
Whatever operation "Fill In The Blank”
is churning in your mind...
You don't even know what
the idea is.
I know that Grace doesn't need you
meddling in her life.
She's a grown adult,
she's also our business partner.
And she's your sister
and my best friend.
All the more reason not
to meddle.
Okay, Ryan St. Nicholas is back in town,
he's her one that got away.
She has never explicitly
said that.
She's had a crush on him since she was
12.
The whole town knows he
feels the same.
They've been friends for years.
If they wanted to date,
they would have by now.
No, they've never had
a chance. Think about it.
Ryan was dating Ryan dated Miranda
in freshman year and then,
when they broke up,
Grace started dating Vince.
- Ugh.
- And then, when they broke up...
Okay, I get it.
But now, they're both single...
I think. Wait.
What are you doing?
I'm just gonna do a quick little social
media stalk,
make sure that he's not in
a relationship.
It doesn't look like he is!
He's single and ready to mingle.
I love you and your little missions,
but it...
now is not the time for another attempt
at operation "Find Grace Love,”
especially not with
Ryan St. Nicholas.
I'm going to order us some dinner.
While I'm gone, don't do any meddling.
No promises.
Well, well, well, look what
the elves dragged in.
Wow! Talk about a glow up.
Lookin' good, Santaman.
- Quinn, how are you, buddy?
- Good.
You know, no one has called me
Santaman since high school.
Ah, it's a waste of a perfectly
good nickname.
I don't know about that.
So, what’s this I hear about
you wanting to sell the place?
Where did you hear that?
Ah, it's just a rumour around town,
since the place has been empty for what,
like five years, now?
Yeah, no. It was just a quick trip
back to get my nan out of this place.
She didn't want to go, but it was time.
She just couldn't handle this place
anymore, you know?
Oh, man, it's just so weird
being back here without her.
Yeah, losing a loved one is
never easy, man.
Hey, everyone loved your nan.
You know, she actually liked you...
even though you spent half your nights out
in out lawn here with...
putting, what? With the large Christmas
decorations all over our lawn.
- That was all Olivia and you know it.
- Oh, Olivia! Alright, pff.
The house is in pretty good shape.
Yeah, I've had people maintaining it,
making sure everything is in working
order. I just...
I'm not sure what I want to do
with it yet.
Well, if you do decide you want to sell,
I have a very interested buyer,
and if you do sell to me, of course,
I could guarantee you that I would fill
this place with a lot of life.
There you go.
Alright, I'll make you a deal.
If I do decide to sell, I'll call you,
let you make the first offer.
Sounds fair?
Sure.
Sounds good, sounds good.
Go Polar Bears, right?
- Hi.
Hey, Grace.
What's going on here?
You boys behaving yourselves?
Always.
Always? Oh, no. I remember more than one
hockey game where the coach
benched you two for...
what did he call it?
Severe competition.
You know, I thought of it more
as passion.
Passion, yeah, that's it.
Passion's the word you're looking for.
Alright, I'll get out of your hair.
Uh... I'm gonna grab a bite at
Beth’s Bistro, if you're free.
Oh, I... I... I have some work
I gotta get done, so...
Okay.
But if my schedule changes,
I'll text you later.
Sounds good.
- You and Quinn, uh? Oh, okay.
- It's complicated.
- Yeah? Oh.
- We're just... hanging out sometimes...
whenever we're both free.
It's nothing serious, we're just the last
two single people left in Ivy Glen.
Anyway, I...
Came here to talk to you about
the Ribbons and Bows Fundraiser.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
- Let me guess, Sami sent you.
- Oh, she did. She was very insistent.
Hmm, it's good to see that Sami will
still do whatever she can
to get what she believes in.
Yeah, but she has a point.
I mean, come on, your nan's fundraiser,
it did a lot of good
for Ivy Glen back in the day and...
you know, with the way things are,
it could a lot of people
if you brought it back.
Listen, I know that's the last thing you
probably want to hear,
but I'll help you, okay?
Anything you need, just consider it done.
I've already made a list of vendors that
I think would work for the place and...
it would really mean a lot to me
for this opportunity, I just...
I love it here.
So?
What do you say? Will you let me help you
revive the Ribbons and Bows Fundraiser?
Please.
I'll make it really easy for you, okay?
Olivia and Jack and I,
we will handle everything.
All you have to do is open up the place
and we will take care of the rest...
Okay, okay, okay.
So, you'll do absolutely everything?
All you have to do is smile and wave,
and you're good at that.
- Okay, you know what? Fine.
Let's do it.
- Okay, great! Yes!
- It could be fun.
- It'll be so much fun!
Okay, so do you want to meet tomorrow
morning at the café,
we could start planning?
- Yeah, let's do that.
- Okay, sounds good.
- Okay, so tomorrow at the café?
- Yeah.
- With Ryan St. Nicholas?
Oh, wow, okay. I'm just gonna
go run an errand.
- Do you want me to go with you?
No, it's okay sweetie, I'll be quick.
I'll see you at home.
- You good?
- Yeah, great. Why?
Just, you know, Ryan.
Come on! He was my high school
crush, Jack, okay? I am so over it.
- I just know he was...
- A great friend, nothing more...
which is great. I love great
friends, they're... great.
Great?
- Stop it.
I'm just trying to be a good
big brother and look out for you.
Okay, you're a great big brother and
I love you, but I'm a big girl, okay?
The charm of Ryan St. Nicholas
has long since passed.
Okay.
Listen, I'm gonna order dinner.
Do you want sweet and sour chicken?
Does that sound good?
- Mm-hmm.
Egg rolls.
- Obviously.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Hey, good timing.
- Hello.
Wow. I've had so many
post-game milkshakes here.
- Oh, yeah.
- Everything is the same.
Yeah.
It's kind of nice how things
don't change.
Yeah, it is.
Alright, let's grab a table.
Thank you.
The key to a great design is a strong
theme and since this is your fundraiser,
I would love to get your thoughts.
- Oh, sorry. That's one of our clients.
I gotta take this.
I will be right back.
Hi, Sarah.
Yeah, it's a good time.
You guys seem pretty busy.
You sure you got time for this?
Yeah, we got this. Come on, I know your
nan's house as well as I know my own.
I mean, I haven't been back to the
St. Nicholas House in a few years, but...
Nothing's changed.
Must be hard, going back there
without her.
Yeah. No, it is.
It's gonna be hard having
Christmas without her.
Yeah, but you know what?
She would be so proud
that you're reviving the Ribbons
and Bows Fundraiser,
that always meant a lot to her.
I was hesitant to do it, but honestly,
feels like the right thing to do.
Hmm.
Will your parents be joining?
They were always the life of the party.
- No, not this year.
They're actually backpacking
through Europe right now.
That's awesome.
I know! I'm so happy they're finally
doing it.
It was always on my bucket list to go
backpacking through Europe.
Yeah, mine too.
We should make that happen, then.
Um... so, this design.
Okay, how about this?
Come over to the house.
We'll go room to room,
see if we spark an inspiration.
That'd be great.
- You gonna get that?
Oh... that's just Quinn. You want
to get some hot chocolates to go?
- Yeah.
- Great.
Okay.
Can we get two hot chocolates
to go, please? Thanks.
- This your work?
- Yeah. Yeah, it is. What do you think?
Meh.
Kidding. The decorations look amazing.
Thanks. And it's really too bad that
we didn't get the contract
to decorate Ivy Glen's downtown
this year.
Yeah, but we will next year.
Thanks.
Hey. I'm gonna head back.
Jack's waiting on me to wrap the gifts
for the children that we're sponsoring
this year.
I'm about two hours late.
I'll see you both soon.
- See you soon.
- Bye.
So, is it weird being back?
I mean, so much has changed.
What do you mean?
Come on, everything about you
is different.
You left this town as a boy in a scraggly
white t-shirt with jeans
and you came back as a...
as a business tycoon in a very,
very posh suit.
- It is bespoke, thank you for noticing.
- Hmm.
Tell me about your business.
Oh, well, we are a full-scale decorating
and design firm
and we do everything from house
remodels all the way
to holiday decorating depending
on the client's needs.
So, what made you get into that?
Uh, my first year in college,
I took a decorating course
and it was just a throwaway course,
but it changed everything, changed me.
I don't know, I always thought you were
gonna do something with fashion.
- Fashion? Why?
You're just so bold, you know?
Do you remember when I bet you
you couldn't wear
my nan's Mrs. Claus outfit
for an entire week?
- I did.
- Oh, you did. You showed up every day
with a wig, the glasses,
that big fluffy dress...
I'm not gonna lie,
I was pretty impressed.
Yeah. Well, mister Bentford
wasn't very impressed.
He called me out in front of the entire
chemistry class, remember that?
Yeah. Well, he never had
a sense of humour anyway.
No, he didn't.
Thank you.
There you go. Thank you.
Keep the change.
You always knew how to make
everyone laugh.
Oh, I don't know about that.
Well, for me, at least.
Since that first day when
I was the new kid in Ivy Glen.
You know, I took my duties
as the unofficial head of the high school
welcoming committee very seriously.
Well, you made that transition
to live with my nan much easier.
I'm glad I could help.
Oh, speaking of help, if you need me to
do anything for the fundraiser,
I know you said that you would
take care of everything,
but if you need help, I'm here,
because that's what friends are for.
Yeah.
We're still friends, though, right?
Oh, come on, of course, we're friends.
We're always gonna be friends.
Listen, I should get going.
Okay. Text me if you want
to come by the house.
Okay.
Grace.
Yeah?
Really good to see you.
Good to see you too,
Ryan St. Nicholas.
I'm telling you,
this is the move!
- No, no.
- Yes, yes, yes!
This could finally be their perfect
moment.
Timing is everything, right?
Plus, Grace deserves her own love story.
This is just a little nudge.
Olivia, please, stop.
You didn't see her.
It affected her, it was so cute.
Like... okay. Do you remember
the Christmas pageant
that your mom talked
us into doing?
The one where Grace and Ryan
thought they were gonna be
background understudies, but then,
got wrangled into playing Mary and Joseph?
Yes, yes, and do you remember how they
were so locked into one another?
Like no one else mattered,
it was just the two of them?
Olivia, they were ten-years-old.
I think they were more focused
on not forgetting their lines
and embarrassing themselves
in front of the whole town.
Okay, maybe, but you didn't
see them at the café.
The way that she was looking
at him,
I have never seen her look
at anyone like that before.
They are so perfect for each other,
the timing just never been right...
until now.
What?
I have a plan.
- You're kidding me.
Mistletoe.
- Isn't mistletoe Grace's thing?
- It's mine, now.
Operation Mistletoe. I am getting them
under this if it is the last thing I do.
Why?
Because, she's my best friend,
and even if she can't see it right now,
this is the right thing for her.
They've never been single
at the same time.
Okay, step one, the café, check.
- You didn't?
- I did, yeah,
but we didn't end up
sitting at the right table.
Umm, but step two, I'm gonna put
it at St. Nicholas House,
and step three, I'm just gonna put
them all over Ivy Glen.
I mean, nothing says romance
like the magic of mistletoe!
You know what? You're right.
Nothing does.
Okay, I got one for the office,
two for St. Nicholas house,
I did one for the café.
- Hey. What 'cha doing?
- Oh! Uh...
just looking for my
lip gloss and I found it.
- Do you want some hot chocolate?
- Yeah, sure.
Um, two hot chocolates, please.
- Hey, Grace, Olivia.
- Quinn, hi.
I'm glad I caught you. I just wanted to
swing by on my way to work
to run something by you.
- What's up?
Okay, I'm working with a major investor,
a luxury condo group
looking to expand into our little town,
how cool is that?
Cool or madly destructive
to our town's integrity?
Olivia. She's just kidding,
Quinn.
She's always been a kidder, huh?
Anyways, I just have to find them
the perfect location and we're good to go,
but I would love for you to
design the space.
Sounds amazing.
It would be huge and it could
put Keene and Rankin on the map,
and it would boost local business.
Mayor Hoffman agrees.
Yeah, we... we love that idea.
That sounds great,
we can't wait to hear more, can we,
Olivia?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Um... oh,
did you want a hot chocolate, Quinn?
Uh, ye... no, no,
I'm good, but talk soon?
- Sure.
- Okay.
- Oh, sorry. Okay.
Wow. I have seen rocks have more
chemistry than you two.
At lest, he's nice and he's smart and
you know, successful.
That's... that checks some boxes.
Well, that's love is,
it's just a box to be checked.
Okay. Listen, I'll see you in a few
hours to get started on the tree.
In a few hours?
Yeah, I told Ryan I'd stop by
the St. Nicholas House
so that we can talk about the design.
You know what?
I should get him a coffee too.
Ah, well, maybe while you're there,
you could go on the porch,
like, really take it all in,
maybe he's there with you.
Okay, I know you, Olivia,
what are you up to?
I... just taking care of our
most important client.
You have a glint in your eye,
got something up your sleeve?
Santa’s elves never reveal
their secrets.
Okay.
I gotta find some fancy
coffee shop.
Hey, right on time. What...
what's this?
A flat white with oat milk
and two sugars
How did you know my coffee
order?
Oh, come on, isn't that
the typical big city order?
Oh, okay. Well, what's your order?
Just in case, you know, I want to return
the favour.
Oh, just a small drip coffee
with two creamers.
- Simple and classic, I like it.
- Yeah.
Oh...
- I did not know that was there.
- Yeah, me neither. Um...
- I mean, we shouldn't, right?
- What? No. Ew.
Ew?
I don't mean like ew, ew,
I just mean...
...why? Did you want to kiss me?
No.
Did you want to kiss me?
- No.
- Okay, then we're good.
- Yeah, totally, totally good.
We should probably just take that down,
though. It's a little dangerous.
- I got it, I got it.
- Hanging up there like that, you know?
- Let's put that right in your purse.
- Great.
- Anyway, it's cold,
so maybe we should just get inside.
- Yeah, okay.
- Alright, let's get started.
Thank you.
- No problem.
Wow!
This is in a lot better shape
than I was expecting,
already done some decorating
too, nice job.
Oh, no, these were my nan's decorations,
we just didn't take them down
after she left.
She always had great taste.
Hum! The smell of this place brings me
right back to high school.
I know. I'd always make
the cleaning crew
use the exact same pine stuff
that my nan would.
Oh. It's nice that some things
stay the same.
Well, I'm starting to realize
that you're not the same at all.
- I'm not?
- No, you're more...
Hilarious? Good-looking?
Wildly well spoken?
You're more yourself. It's cool to see
you like this, focused, in your element.
It's really nice of you to say.
Well, I meant it.
Mm! You know, that was always
my favourite of your nan's decorations.
- This one?
- Yeah!
This is my eighth grade
masterpiece.
Eighth grade?
You made that in eighth grade?
Hold on, are you... mocking my
art skills?
No, I would never.
I'm being serious, I love it.
I mean, she has a lot of great
decorations,
but that one, that's the best.
Man. So why did you leave it up
after all these years?
I just didn't have the heart
to take it down.
I hired a caregiver for my nan
after grad school
and I realized I wouldn't be able to make
it out here as frequently as I wanted to.
I should have visited more.
The last few months here,
the caregiver said
that she thought every morning
was Christmas.
I just couldn't take that away
from her.
I'm glad you didn't.
I even went and decorated her room at
the care facility by my place.
Stayed up for five years until
she passed.
Well, there's nothing like the Christmas
spirit to get through hard times.
You know, what do you think
about adding to her collection?
What do you mean?
I mean, we don't have a theme yet
and this is really beautiful.
I mean, of course, we'd have to add more
and update a bit,
but I think it's a really good starting
point... if you'd like.
- I would like that.
- Great.
Glad to know we're on
the same page.
I mean, we still need to get a cohesive
theme to bring it all together, but yeah.
Okay, which room is next?
Right here.
So, you and Quinn, I know you
said it wasn't anything serious.
- Look, it's really not, okay?
We're good friends, you know?
It's nice to have somebody to go
to the movies with.
- Okay, so hypothetically...
- Mm-hmm?
If someone were to ask
you out...
Well, I would have to evaluate,
you know?
See if it fits to my work schedule.
Okay. Makes sense.
How about you? I'm sure a lot
of ladies love a bespoke suit.
- Some of them do.
Okay.
- I am kind of in the same boat.
- Yeah?
Everything at the firm is just
going so well that...
I don't know, I just haven't given
any thought to dating.
Oh. Well, you know, I am just so
relieved to know that we both grew up
to be adults with a great
work-life balance.
Ugh. I mean, my last
relationship was...
gosh, five years ago, maybe?
- Oof, what happened?
He was a really great guy,
he was in sales and...
I mean, he was really nice,
but we just...
ugh, you know, we didn't have that
thing, you know? That spark.
And I think we both knew it, but we were
just so good on paper
and we were trying to
make it work, but...
I realized that wasn't what was
best for both of us.
- No one else since?
- Oh, couple dates here and there.
- Yeah, Quinn, right?
- Okay, but chemistry is hard to fake.
Oh, you tell me. These days, it's like
finding lightning in a bottle.
You know, it's funny, I feel like I'm at
that age
where I can finally come up
for air.
For years, I just had my nose to
the grindstone, working late,
just doing whatever it takes to get
the job done,
not giving it a second thought.
- And now?
- Now?
I don't know, I just... kind of feel like
there's a shift in my life.
Everything that's happened in this
last year with my nan passing,
with realizing how much time
and dedication I put into work,
time that I'll never get back.
I mean, it's like someone turned on
the lights and I could see everything
that I gave up to get what I have.
There's still time.
- Not with my nan.
I mean, yes, I moved her as close to me as
possible so I could spend as much time
with her as I could, but...
it's never enough, you know?
I mean, she was the only family
that I had and now...
And now, you can start your
own family from the ground up.
If you want to.
- Should... we go see the sun porch?
Yeah, sure.
Do you remember sophomore year
when my nan hosted
that huge Christmas dinner?
Oh, come on, are you kidding?
The first time I had Christmas
Goose was in this very house.
Yeah? You had it since?
Oh, come on, nobody in this
town makes Christmas Goose.
Oh, and her hot chestnut stuffing,
I still dream about it to this day.
I know. I... I tried to make it last
year when my nan left me her recipe and...
yeah, it was a massive fail.
I burnt everything.
Well, maybe we could recreate
it some time.
I happen to be surprisingly
a very good cook.
Well, if your baking is any indication
of your cooking, I can't wait to try.
Oh, it's like stepping back in time,
I just love it.
Oh, yes. Okay, strike a pose.
You haven't aged a bit.
Do you remember your Christmas
cookies you used to make?
My nan used to love those.
She said it reminded her
of her childhood.
I tried to recreate them and it
just wasn't the same.
Are you talking about my
Christmas sugar cookies?
I had no idea.
Yeah. Well, if I didn't tell you,
I meant to.
Well, then, I'll have to make you
a batch while you're in town.
Please.
Have dinner with me.
Come on, Ryan, it's like
11 o'clock in the morning.
- I know, I meant later.
- Oh.
You know, I would love to,
but I have to decorate that Christmas
tree tonight.
- Yeah, I forgot.
- Yeah.
Okay, what about another time?
As friends, just friends,
old friends.
Yeah, maybe. Um... let me
check my schedule.
Oh, I forgot your busy schedule.
Let me just check, okay? Please.
So, Town Square, do you know
what you're doing yet?
Yeah, I do.
I'll tell you, but you gotta keep it
a secret.
I like things to be a surprise.
- Lips are sealed.
- Alright.
And I'll even show you some
of my designs.
So, I was thinking that I wanted
to tell a Christmas story, right?
I want it to capture the meaning
of Christmas, how it feels,
I want it to be a perfect blend
of the past and present.
It's a lot of pressure for
a tree, isn't it?
Yes and no, okay?
Listen, I like my designs to tell a tale
and even if I don't have it completely
figured out yet, I...
We should get a tree for this place,
a 14-footer.
You know, we could totally do that.
14 feet? That is huge.
Yeah. Well, go big or go home, right?
We want to make a statement.
And I think we could put it on the sun
porch, just like nan used to.
Oh, by the way, I spoke to Tim down
at the market and he's going to donate
all the beverages for the fundraiser
and the café is gonna do
the catering free of cost.
Wow, that's... so generous.
I know, people, they're just,
they're so eager to help.
You know, this fundraiser really is doing
a lot of good for everybody.
I guess so.
It just feels right.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go get some decorations,
maybe I'll get some inspiration.
Yes. I will take some pictures
and maybe I'll get inspired.
Hm...
Hm.
Hey, Ryan?
What's up?
What are you doing tonight?
Want to decorate a Christmas
tree with me?
You have the whole town support.
Yes, I agree.
Okay. Chat soon.
Apparently, Grace and Olivia have gotten
everything off the ground
for Ryan's Ribbons and Bows
Christmas Fundraiser.
He actually sounded excited.
- Was that him on the phone?
- Oh, yes.
He asked me to get the word out,
do some publicity.
Hmm. Sounds like he wants one last
hurrah before he sells the place.
Sells the place?
Mm-hmm, I'm gonna make
him a great offer,
and then you, Madame Mayor,
will have a site for those luxury
condos we discussed.
I'd have to see the proposal first.
- You know that a first-class state-of
- the-art condo complex
would be great for local business.
Just think about all of the money that
would be poured into Ivy Glen's
restaurants and shops...
- I've already said I liked your pitch.
...By residents enjoying the new
luxury amenities.
We both know that the site of
the St. Nicholas House
is quite literally the perfect location.
Point is, I think this could be
exactly what we both need.
I mean, you want a second term
as mayor, right, Sami?
Boost the local economy,
increase the tax base
and you’re a shoo-in.
Okay. Okay, let's talk about
this more at the office tomorrow.
I want to see those
numbers again.
Okay. Thank you, Sami.
Oh, no, no, I got it. Thank you.
Thank you.
That is a great tree.
It is gonna take us forever
to decorate it.
Oh, I have a plan.
I'm going to tie together the old
and the new,
figured Mayor Hoffman
and all of the donors will love it.
Hey.
- Where do you want this?
Over by the tree would be great.
Right away, boss.
Thanks.
What?
- Nothing.
- Thank you all for coming.
- Alright, let's do this!
You can take these over there and work
on that side of the tree
and I'll have the crew
finish the top.
- Sounds good.
- Thanks.
This looks phenomenal.
Yeah! Wait till you see how the design
ties in to the one at St. Nicholas House.
Spreading the themes across locations,
I like it.
Yeah. I just thought it might
encourage giving.
And these are so gorgeous,
where did they come from?
Oh, I might have had something
to do with that.
- Ryan!
- Jack.
By the way, I'm so sorry I missed
the wedding, guys. Congratulations.
No, we missed you,
but we understand, you're busy.
Yeah, but I'm always busy
and that needs to change.
Okay, I gotta go back
to the tree.
Yeah, I'll meet you over there
in a second.
I'm going to get the samples for
the Peterson tree. Do you need anything?
Grace? Do you need anything?
- No, I'm good.
Okay.
Bye.
So, things went well at St. Nicholas House
this morning?
- Yeah. Yeah... you could say that.
I mean, so well that he lent
you his nan's decorations.
Hmm.
Did you see any hanging
decorations that you liked?
Like greenery, festive greenery, no?
- Well, well, well, look at all this!
- Hey.
- Hey! I was just in the neighbourhood,
thought I'd pop by.
- Oh.
Okay. Well, I'm gonna go see if
the crew needs help.
Okay, thank you. What's this?
Coffee. Five creams,
nine sugars.
It's good, right?
Yeah, it's my go-to.
Hmm.
Anyway, I gotta run, the proposal goes
live this afternoon.
- Oh, good luck with that.
- Thanks.
Thanks. If it all goes well,
it could change all of our lives.
Yeah.
Anyway, I just wanted to say, this has
been a lot of fun,
us reconnecting and hanging out,
just like high school.
Yeah. Um...
...listen, about that, Quinn,
I think that you're a
really great guy, okay?
And I love your drive and your
ambition and...
I just...
I don't think that I can do this anymore.
I... I've really enjoyed spending
time with you, I have, but I...
I think I'm just looking for
something a little more serious.
Oh.
Oh, I see, um...
To be honest, I'm not sure I'm in a place
to settle down right now.
I mean, I really like you, I do,
I think you're an amazing woman,
but...
I feel like I have so much going on.
I... I feel like I need to focus
right now, I hope you understand.
- Yeah, your projects.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's gonna be huge.
I mean, bigger than...
...than the hockey team making it to
the state championship our senior year.
- Wow. Quinn, that is really, really big.
- Right?
Yeah, mm-hmm.
I've... I've really enjoyed
our time together.
If you do change your mind,
I'm down for a dinner.
- Oh.
- Or a heist movie.
Or maybe even a romcom.
- Okay, deal. Good luck today.
- Thanks.
- Yeah. Thanks for this.
Listen, thank you so much for
your help today.
We quite literally could not have
done that without you, Ryan.
I'm happy to help.
Oh, also, I wanted to give you guys this.
- Oh.
That should cover any of the expenses.
I know you said that all the food
and beverages were completely donated,
but I don't want to put anyone out.
We're not doing this halfway,
so anything we don't use,
we can donate to the food bank.
It's incredibly generous.
Oh, sorry, I gotta run. Grace,
this is the Gregsons
about us potentially redoing their
kitchen and living room.
- Yeah, I can come with you.
- No, no, no, you stay, I got it.
Okay. Our samples are on my desk.
Okay, amazing. Thank you. Bye.
You kids have fun!
- Thank you for this.
- It's what my nan would have wanted.
- Yeah.
And you know what?
She'd be proud having all of her
decorations in Town Square on the tree.
Mm-hmm.
She loved it here.
So, what gave you the idea to do this?
Oh. Well, I found this
and I thought it was the perfect blend
tying together the past and present.
Should we get back to it?
- Uh... yeah, okay.
Actually, you know what? I have
a few errands I need to run, so...
Yeah, okay. I don't want to take
advantage of your free labour,
but it has been very helpful.
Listen, if you want to get that
dinner later...
if you're still interested.
Oh... yeah, no, we'll talk
about that tomorrow.
Yeah. Tomorrow, okay. Great.
- Ryan? Hi.
- Jack.
What can I do for you?
I just wanted to drop this off,
Grace left it in Town Square.
Uh... she'll be grateful for that.
She'd be lost without this thing.
I keep trying to tell her to go
digital, but nope.
Sounds like Grace.
You hungry? I was just
about to order pizza.
Oh, I couldn't interrupt.
No, come on, I’d be grateful
for the break.
Okay, let's do it.
I do not remember that.
Well, yeah, because you
already graduated.
You were too cool to hang out
with these lowly sophomores.
Well, that's not true!
Okay, that's partially true,
but I was wrong.
Now, I'm married to my sister's best
friend, working for both of them.
And what a pair they are.
A powerhouse dynamic duo.
I'm lucky to be in her orbit.
So, are you enjoying being home?
Yeah, I am.
I was a little nervous coming back,
but... mm-hmm.
Well, you did wait long enough.
I didn't mean to, it's just the years
kept piling on and before I knew it...
wow, yeah, 15 years.
Do you regret any of it?
Honestly, no, because it got
to where I am today,
and yes, I love my job, but...
You want someone to share it all with.
When did you get so sentimental?
I just think that as you get older,
you start to realize what really
matters in life.
I mean, sure, success is great,
but if you don't have someone to share
it with, what does it matter?
A little cheesy, but you're right.
At the end of the day,
it's all about connection.
How's working with your spouse?
It's not for everyone,
I'll give you that, but for us...
she's my best friend,
a co-pilot.
You're really lucky.
But don't get me wrong,
it takes work.
But without her,
none of it matters.
You and Grace seem to be hitting
it off again.
Liv’s always thought you two
would end up together.
Really?
What makes her say that?
Grace has always been more
herself around you,
plus, I think the best relationships
start as friendships.
Well, I'm happy she found someone,
even if it is with Quinn.
Okay, one, I love that your rivalry
with Quinn is alive and well
all these years later, and two, trust me,
I know my sister,
there's nothing going on with that guy.
She said the same to me,
but when I saw them at the tree...
I don't know, kind of seem like
the opposite to me.
And he's very...
Handsome? Tall? Charming?
I was gonna say kind,
but yeah, that works.
It's been really nice, having him back.
- It is, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Do you know how long
he's staying?
Let me talk to Grace about that.
No, you do not need to talk to
Grace about that.
- Talk to me about what?
- Oh.
- Your love life.
- Gee, thanks.
Hey, Ryan.
What are you doing here?
He stopped by to give you
your sketch book.
Yeah, you...
left this at Town Square.
Oh, thank you so much,
you're a lifesaver.
Okay. Jack, we gotta go.
Remember?
- We do?
- Yeah!
Bye. See you both later.
- Woah...
...did I forget something?
Do we forget... do you have my coat?
- I have your coat, let's go.
Uh...
Okay. Um...
I don't know about you, but I could
go for a sugar cookie, right now.
- Okay, sure.
Alright.
- I can't believe we're doing this.
I mean, we're actually gonna
have cookies for dinner.
- Are you mad at it?
- I mean... no, of course not.
Hey, are you sure everything in
this kitchen still works?
Oh, for sure. I got a maintenance team
here all the time making sure everything
is in working order.
Gotta protect your investments.
- Investments? What does that mean?
You know, yeah, it's my family
house, but it's also an asset.
Oh.
- What?
- Hmm.
Uh... that eyebrow raise begs to differ.
It's just an asset? I mean, come on,
is that really how you see this place?
That’s what owning property
is, right?
- Let's make some cookies, hmm?
- Okay.
Okay, so first of all, if you're gonna
help me with this,
you might want to take
off your suit jacket.
- Um... okay. Yeah, you're right.
Sorry, it's just a habit.
It's your suit of armour, huh?
Exactly, yes, a suit of armour.
Okay, so tell me about your work.
Um... well, basically,
I'm a financial advisor,
I help people achieve their
long-term financial goals
in the shortest time possible.
Oh. Sounds fun. Do you like it?
Yeah, I actually do.
It's really rewarding when I see
the look on my client's face
when I help them reach their goals
and I double their investment.
Great.
Alright, so all you have to do
is just, you're gonna take this,
put a little flour on there and you're
gonna give it some easy pressure
back and forth.
Here you go.
Okay.
Like that?
- Yeah.
Okay.
So, how long are you staying
in town?
I don't know. This fundraiser is keeping
me here a bit longer and to be honest,
I'm not that mad at it.
I'm kind of enjoying being back.
Oh, "Actually enjoying being back."
Well, what were you expecting?
Well, I don't know. I didn't know what
I was walking into, it's been so long.
Well, are you happy with what you found?
Surprisingly, yeah.
Makes me want to spend more time here.
I don't think I'm doing this right.
- I'll take over.
- Yeah.
- Do you have cookie cutters?
Uh... yeah, I think so. Just...
Oh, here we go.
- Perfect.
There is so much junk in this house.
Junk? Listen, I happen to think that
there's a lot of things with sentimental
value in this house.
So, what are your plans for this
house anyway, uh?
I mean, it's such a magical place,
it makes me sad to think about it empty.
Me too. You're right, I'm not doing this
place justice, my nan loved this place.
I know she did.
I should have brought her back
for one last Christmas.
No. Hey, you look at me,
Ryan St. Nicholas, okay?
I know that it was not an easy decision,
moving your nan away from this place,
but I also know you and I know
that you took great care of her.
You know what?
What you're doing right now,
reviving her legacy with
the Ribbons and Bows Fundraiser,
that would make her very,
very proud.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
You're... you're right.
Yeah. Alright, you want to cut
some cookies?
- Yes.
- Great.
Okay. Ooh, I'll grab this one
right here.
Perfect.
Alright.
How did I do?
Nailed it!
Hopefully, it tastes better
than it looks.
It's the moment of truth.
I can confirm, it does.
A plus on your baking skills and
C minus for my decorating skills.
Hey, no, I would give that
a solid B minus.
Uh-huh, that's generous.
Oh, sorry, it's my tree guy.
- You got a tree guy?
- Yeah.
Hey, Billy. Did you get my
message about the tree earlier? Mm-hmm.
Uh... 14 feet would be ideal.
Oh.
Yeah, no, that's okay,
thanks anyway.
Mm-hmm. Bye.
Tree problems?
I just really wanted a 14-foot tree,
but all the big ones are gone within
a 50-mile radius, so...
...anyway, I didn't realize how late
it was getting.
I have a big day tomorrow,
but this was so much fun.
So...
- Oh, no, no, no, I got it.
What? No, I am not making you
clean up your entire kitchen by yourself.
Okay, I'll make you a deal.
Leave the cookies
and we're even.
Okay. Deal.
So, will I see you at the Christmas tree
lighting tomorrow?
I wouldn't miss it.
Great. Maybe we can get that
dinner we talked about.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Me too.
Alright.
Well, get out of here.
Thanks for a good night.
Okay, party people! We've got
T-minus three hours until showtime!
Hey, Jack and I are gonna grab a pizza
and watch old Christmas movies
after the tree lighting
if you want to join.
Oh, I can't, I'm having dinner
with Ryan.
- Wait, you're what?
- Just as friends.
Okay, you go home,
you do a face mask,
you paint your nails,
you, you give yourself a blowout.
You can just meet me here before
the tree lighting.
But we have work to do!
I know, I've got it covered.
You go, you go!
- Oh, I...
- Wear a cute dress! Wear heels!
Yes!
Oh, we are so close.
Operation Mistletoe is almost a success.
- Olivia...
- They are going for dinner tonight,
for dinner, do you hear me?
I just need to pull more sprigs.
- I think you need to take a breath.
- No, I need more mistletoe.
Do you think Grace will be angry if
she finds out that you're behind
all the mysterious mistletoe that keeps
popping up around town?
No, I think that she would thank me.
I mean, Christmas is the most romantic
time of the year,
I'm just giving them a little nudge.
Love you. Wish me luck!
Love you.
Hey.
Hi.
Should be any minute now.
Is it weird that I kind of feel like a
little kid right now?
- No, not at all.
I get excited every time I go to
a Christmas tree lighting.
I mean, especially when we're
the ones in charge of decorating it.
Yeah.
Do you think Sami likes it?
I think we'll have to wait for
the tree to be lit up to know that.
Hey, do you remember when we bet
that you couldn't make it
to the top of the Town Square
Christmas tree?
I can't believe you actually tried
to do it.
I made it halfway up that tree before
Mayor Dodds started to call my parents.
Yeah. Please don't do that
tonight.
No promises.
Wow! Look at that, the whole
group's here!
Go Polar Bears!
Come on, go Polar Bears!
Go Polar Bears.
- Hey, Grace.
- Quinn.
It's great having Santaman back, huh?
Yeah, it is, actually.
Gather round, everyone, it's
time to light the tree!
- Okay.
Merry Christmas!
Oh, it's so beautiful! I don't think
I've ever seen one prettier tree
than this Christmas tree.
- Oh, I think that Sami likes it.
- I think she loves it.
- You guys did a beautiful job.
- Thank you.
And huge thanks to you for all your help
and letting use your grandma's
decorations.
- I'm happy they came in handy.
- Yeah.
Oh, the volunteers are gonna drop by
the house tomorrow to decorate
based on Grace's designs.
Did she mention we're gonna leave
the old decorations up?
I want them to be part of it so we can
build upon Mrs. St. Nicholas’ legacy.
- I love that. I'll let them know.
- Okay.
You know, I think I forgot how much
I missed Christmas here.
Oh yeah?
- So, should we go eat?
- Yeah, I'm starving.
Oh, man, I'd love to,
I would, but I've...
I've got this investor thing I need to
finish, but let's talk soon.
I've got some things
I want to run by you.
Bye, Grace.
- Sure.
Bye, Quinn.
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
You did not say that.
I did. It was my first board meeting,
I had no clue what was going on.
Oh, come on! Even I know that you
don't comment on your boss's lunch order.
I thought it was helping.
- You can get that if you need.
No. That is business,
it can wait till business hours.
I'm sorry, who are you and what have you
done with Ryan St. Nicholas?
Well, it is Christmas time and since
I've been back here
and staying at the St. Nicholas House,
it's made me realize that maybe over
the past few years, my priorities have
been a bit out of whack.
Yeah, I can relate to that.
You know, my parents actually invited me
on their Christmas European backpacking
tour and I said no because I had to work.
I mean, who does that?
At least, Jack stayed back
with you.
Yeah. Yeah, but he's gonna celebrate
with Olivia and her family, so...
How about this? Next Christmas,
we'll plan it out,
we'll have a work-free
Christmas.
So, does that mean you're
coming back next Christmas too?
What?
To be honest, I was actually thinking
about selling the St. Nicholas House.
You what?
You were right, it's sad that it's just
been sitting there vacant all this time.
Yeah, but...
I mean, come on,
you can't just sell it.
Oh, I know that now.
I think I was just avoiding it because
of what it meant, that without my nan...
I'm alone, so...
You're not alone. Listen,
you have your friends and...
Ryan, no matter how far away you are,
how much time has passed
or wherever life takes us,
you'll always have me.
You know that.
I missed you, Grace.
I missed you too, Ryan.
We're not technically under it.
You're right. Technically,
the bar is under it.
Yeah.
Can I walk you home?
Sure, I'd love that.
Hey, can you do me a favour?
Of course.
Can you promise not to wait so long next
time before you come back home?
- I won't.
- Okay, good.
Alright, if you had to watch one
Christmas movie
for the rest of your life,
what would it be?
Easy, A Christmas Carol.
Really? Why?
Because it has a lot
of important lessons in it.
What, like, "Don't count your money
every day, all day,
or your Christmas
spirit will be zapped?"
More like, "Anyone can change their life
and no matter where you are,
choices you made, you can pivot."
Wow! Says the boy who thought
his life would be over
if he didn't make valedictorian.
Well, thankfully, I didn't
peak in high school.
Speaking of high school.
- Mm-hmm.
When is the last time you went
pranking?
You mean like what Quinn
and Olivia used to do
with the giant ornaments in our yard?
I can safely say it's been
years, why?
Because it's my favourite
thing to do during the holidays.
- Oh yeah?
- And I think we should do it.
Are you in? Are you... yeah? Okay.
Oh, Quinn has done a lot with
his parents' old place.
You know, he is a real estate
developer.
I know, but I always thought he would do
something in high school
so he'd never have to leave.
You know he never misses a game?
Yeah, that makes sense.
You ever go with him?
Yeah, the homecoming
a few times... a bunch of us.
Hmm.
Do you remember when we TPd
his house seven nights in a row?
The last night, his dad was waiting
for us, sitting in the window.
Quinn told me he loved it,
made him feel important.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That's so cute. Oh.
I'm sorry Olivia is missing this.
I don't know, I kinda like
that it's just the two of us.
(nervous chuckle
Okay, let's go.
- Shush! Gotta be quiet.
Shush!
Shush.
- It's magnificent.
Oh, I wish I could see his
face in the morning.
- I know he's gonna feel so important.
- Sssh.
Let's get out of here,
we have to go!
Run!
Okay, thanks. Bye.
- What was that?
Still no dice on the 14-foot tree
for St. Nicholas House,
but I stayed up all night last night
and I was able to finalize the design.
Oh, it looks like something
from A Christmas Carol.
Thanks. It's going for a Charles
Dickens' Christmas,
Ribbons and Bows edition.
Tall order, but I love it.
I just want it to be special
for his nan.
Not for him?
- Hey!
- Hey.
Hi.
I was just about to head over to
your house. The volunteers will be there
any minute to help us decorate.
Oh, okay. Well, I'll give you a ride.
I have another surprise for you.
Great.
Okay, you don't need to gloat.
I'm not gloating, this is good.
This is good.
I need mistletoe.
Okay.
What's all this about?
- It's your surprise.
You said 14 feet, right?
How did you...
where did you...
You're not the only one with
a tree guy.
Oh!
Okay, but you're sure
it's 14 feet?
Better be.
Gosh, I'm gonna cry.
11, 12, 13, 14! It's perfect.
Perfect!
Oh, my goodness.
- You guys nailed it.
Okay. They will help you put
it wherever you want.
Uh... how about on the sun porch,
where nan used to put it?
Yeah.
Um... if you put it on the sun porch,
pretty please. Thank you.
I can't believe you did this.
Oh, you know, always happy
to help.
Now, we just gotta decorate the thing.
Okay, so I was thinking, A Christmas
Carol is your favourite movie, right?
So I used that to finalize my design
last night
and I was thinking that's the perfect
blend of old and new.
It signifies change, but also...
- How some things stay the same?
Yes.
But the real question is,
"Can we pull it off?"
Um... oh, I think we can, Ryan
St. Nicholas, yes.
Hi! Hi, everyone. Oh, thank you
so much for coming.
We'll meet you right inside.
- Thank you, thank you.
- I think we can do this.
- Thank you guys.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go decorate this house.
- After you.
Alright.
No, no, no. We... yeah, we got this.
The Mayor approved the plan, so we can
move forward with the deal.
I'm closing on the land any day, now.
Oh, yeah, it's gonna be great.
Go Polar Bears!
This one...
Right...
I think you got it.
Oh, thank you so much for your help.
Can't wait for you all to
celebrate with us tomorrow.
I couldn't bribe you with dinner,
could I?
Yeah, dinner would be great.
Alright. I'll find us some
takeout menus.
By the way, everything looks perfect,
but I'm not surprised at all.
Thank you.
Okay.
Where are you going?
I'm just gonna swing by St. Nicholas
House on the way home.
Why?
- To hang decorations.
- Olivia...
Grace said that they haven't kissed yet
and by my calculations,
they've been under
the mistletoe three time,
still no kiss.
We're running out of time!
I think it's time to give
Operation Mistletoe a rest, my love.
Okay. I just want to try one more thing
and then, I will, I promise.
He’s leaving, Liv.
No, not if I can convince him
he has a reason to stay.
Wish me luck.
- Good luck.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Wow!
This place looks great!
Thanks.
Really.
A little old school for my taste,
but still pretty nice!
- What can I do for you, Quinn?
Is Ryan around?
I sent him a text about some papers
I need him to sign.
Oh, what kind of papers?
Shoot!
Between you and me, I think...
I think it's time this place got a little
bit of a facelift, don't you?
I wasn't under the impression
he was selling.
Oh, no, he's definitely gonna sell.
Everybody has a price and
I think I might have found his.
Thank you for the ornaments on
the lawn, by the way.
Such a blast from the past.
- Olivia, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
What are you doing here?
And what is all this?
- It's just...
- Mistletoe?
I can explain.
Wait, are you the one that's been
putting it all over the place?
- I was just trying to help.
- Help with what?
Oh, hey, Olivia. Were
you in on the lawn gag too?
The what?
- Hello, I'm back.
Oh, there he is.
Oh.
- What's going on?
- Can we talk for a second?
I want to run something by you
about the sale.
I don't know,
I haven't decided if I'm gonna...
What? Come on, man!
This place has sat vacant for years.
Sami already approved the plans.
Wait, Sam...
your project was Ryan's house?
You didn't think that was an important
detail to share, Quinn?
Picture it, okay? This place
completely demolished and its place,
a brand new state of the art world-class
high-end condo complex.
I can't wait to see your bid to decorate
the place,
I think it's gonna be a great
collaboration.
And Sami has already given us
the green light to start demo
at the top of the new year.
Bro, this place will no longer
be your burden.
- Okay, I'm just gonna...
- What is that?
Oh. You know, the mistletoe
that keeps popping up everywhere,
that was Olivia.
What mistletoe?
- That mistletoe, Quinn.
Wait, are you two...
is that why you cut things off
with me?
Grace, he's not sticking around.
He's about to run back
to his life in New York.
He's too good for Ivy Glen, remember?
That's why he hasn't lived here
in the last 15 years.
So, whatever little fantasy
he's had you wrapped up in
the last couple days, it's not real.
I bet you anything he's already
booked his flight
for first thing Christmas morning.
I mean, the only reason he came
back here was to sell the place.
Is that true?
No. Yes...
I don't know.
I just wanted to see if there
was anything left for me here.
Is there?
Okay.
Grace.
Let her go, man. Let her go,
you've done enough.
Let's just sit down, have a cup
of hot cocoa and discuss these numbers.
I think you're gonna be very happy.
My investors are presenting
a very generous offer,
all you have to do is sign the papers
and we're good to go.
Come on, man! This is the best
thing for everyone!
I should have told you about
Operation Mistletoe.
I should've told you about
Yeah, you should have.
I'm sorry, I was just trying to make
this Christmas special for you
and I was hoping if I got
you and Ryan together,
that would be enough
to make him stay.
Guess I was wrong.
Listen, it's not your fault, okay?
I'm the one who got wrapped in the idea
of what it would be like
if Ryan St. Nicholas actually
stayed in Ivy Glen.
Both of us know that would never happen,
Operation Mistletoe or not.
I can't believe he's selling
to Quinn.
I can.
- You don't mean that.
- No, I do. Quinn was right.
I got swept up in a fantasy.
Listen, you're a really good friend,
but lay off the mistletoe for me
for the foreseeable future.
I kind of need a break.
- I can do that.
- Okay.
How much mistletoe did you have, though?
So much.
It's not too bad.
Okay.
Oh, still coming.
And full disclosure, there is some
hanging in your apartment,
just to be safe.
- Great.
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'm gonna be fine.
I think.
Yeah.
You will.
Good morning. You can setup
the catering in the kitchen.
- Thank you.
There is a row of lights in the sitting
room that still needs to be hung.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Alright.
Oh, good morning.
- Morning.
Oh, Olivia, wait. Have you
talked to Grace?
'Cause she's not answering her phone.
I think she needs a moment.
You know, I didn't mean to
lead her on, I just...
...I didn't realize how much
I enjoyed being with her.
- Hmm.
- And I know, selfish, guilty.
Because you're leaving.
I feel like no matter what
I do, it's the wrong choice.
Okay. Well, I'm gonna start
setting up for tonight.
Sorry about the mistletoe.
- Well,
I should have realized
it was you.
(gentle music
Right there is perfect, thank you.
Thanks, guys.
Okay.
Wow! Looks great, thank you.
It's all Grace.
Well, we're almost done, so if you want
to head out, I can take care of the rest.
I'm almost finished.
You think she's gonna show tonight?
It's not like Grace to bail
on a commitment.
I hope you're right.
You know, if you decided to sell,
I don't think anyone would blame you,
but just for the record,
I think we all really enjoyed
having you back.
Wow.
Uh...
Who's there?
What were you planning on
doing with that?
Uh... nothing, I don't know.
I just thought it would...
look better there.
Okay. Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you,
I was just making a few last tweaks.
I wanted to put one more ornament
on the tree.
Doesn't really go with
the design aesthetic, but okay.
Well, it happens to be a very
sentimental ornament
and that's the key to any good design.
Ryan, I...
- Grace, I...
Go ahead.
These last few days have been
amazing.
It's made me realize how much
of myself
I've shut off since I've left this place.
Spending these days with you has kind of
been like my ghost of Christmas past.
It's made me realize what I want
in my life for my future.
Which is?
A life with balance.
A life spending time
with people I love.
In a place that...
feels like home.
Well, Grace, I...
I gotta say, I knew you would pull
it off.
- Pull off what?
Oh, the event hasn't even started
yet and there's a lineup
outside of people ready to donate.
You know, reviving the Ribbons and Bows
Fundraiser
was a very good plan,
if I do say do myself.
Oh, and nice tie-in with the tree
in the Time Square, mm, perfect.
I'm sorry, I'm just so thrilled
that everything is working out perfectly.
So, you're not mad about
losing the condo complex?
What?
Oh, uh...
I'm not selling St. Nicholas House.
You're not?
No. You were right, it's more
than an asset, it's my legacy.
I mean, luxury condo complexes are
great to bring in to new residents,
but I feel like it's more important to
focus on building up
the community we already have.
I couldn't agree more,
and if things go smooth today,
I want to sit down and talk with you about
doing an official partnership
with Ivy Glen and the St. Nicholas House.
Oh, now that is something
I could really get behind.
Oh!
Oh, Olivia! Grace, I spoke to
the town council and they all agree.
The example you're setting here
with this fundraiser
has everyone blown away.
- Oh.
So, I look forward to hiring Keene
and Rankin
for all of the city's upcoming
decoration needs.
Thank you so much!
Oh, honey, can we check if the greeters
are in place?
Thank you so much,
because I think it is five o'clock.
Should we let everyone in?
- Yeah.
- We got to get this show on the road!
- Let's do it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for coming.
We wouldn't be here if it weren't
for the generosity of Ryan St. Nicholas.
So please, Ryan,
would you do us the honours?
- Of course.
And first off, big thank you
to Mayor Hoffman for helping convince me
to do this and all of you for making
this possible.
As you know, this was
my grandmother's house,
and in her honour,
I invite all of you into the Ribbons
and Bows Christmas Fundraiser.
And none of this would have been
possible
if it wasn't for the beautiful
artistry of Grace Rankin.
Oh, and the help of my friends,
Jack and Olivia. Give them a hand.
Alright, merry Christmas!
Come on in!
Thank you guys.
Merry Christmas, thank you.
Merry Christmas.
I'd say that was a success.
Yeah, I mean, we raised enough to cover
the food bank,
the kids after school arts program
and the community centre senior’s events.
That's amazing!
And a huge thanks to you.
Well, thank you for being
my ghost of Christmas everything.
Oh, that's a title I will
gladly accept.
Okay, I'm gonna go tell Sami.
Mayor Hoffman.
- Yes.
- Just call me Sami.
- Oh1
It's weird having my friends
call me Mayor Hoffman.
- Thank you so much because honestly,
I don't know if I was gonna
be able to stick to that.
Sami, will you please meet me outside?
I just want to take some formal pictures
while the photographer is still here.
Absolutely.
I know that we agreed
I’d lay off the mistletoe,
but that doesn't mean you have to.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
So...
...what was it you were gonna
say to me earlier?
I probably should have told
you this back in high school, but...
What's that?
I'm in love with you.
I always have been.
And you know what? I think
I might stick around for a while.
Keep my feet on the ground
and who knows,
maybe wear a t-shirt and jeans
a couple days a week.
How does that sound?
Well, what about your clients
in New York?
Well, I can fly back to New York,
take meetings and do the rest from here.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Then, I just have one last
question for you.
- What?
- Can you do me a favour?
Can you hold this up for me?
I'm kind of short.
- I got you.
Like that?
- Yeah. You know, apparently,
it's bad luck if you don't kiss someone
you love under a mistletoe.
Oh, really?
Mm-hmm.
Guess we're gonna have to reinstate
Operation Mistletoe
'cause we wouldn't want any bad luck
around here, would we?
- I love you, Ryan St. Nicholas.
Happy?
Oh, I am just warming up.
For what?
Operation New Year’s Engagement.
- Yeah.
Seriously?
- Oh, yeah.
- No.
- Yes! Yes!
- I'm not doing that.